blackfridaynewstoday.com 2016-10-17

# Privacy Policy - Black Friday News Today

blackfridaynewstoday.com, has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the [www.blackfridaynewstoday.com](http://www.blackfridaynewstoday.com/ "Reliableremodeler") site.

. **[What information does blackfridaynewstoday.com collect?](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#collect)**

. **[What organization is collecting the information?](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#organization)**

. **[What does blackfridaynewstoday.com do with the data it collects?](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#data)**

. **[With whom does blackfridaynewstoday.com share data?](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#share)**

. **[What choices are available regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#choices)**

. **[How can I update or correct my information?](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#update)**

. **[How can I delete my information?](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#delete)**

. **[What procedures have been designed to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Calorie- Smart.com’s control?](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#protect)**

. **[What about privacy policies for sites to which blackfridaynewstoday.com links?](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#policies)**

. **[What happens to my information if blackfridaynewstoday.com merges with or is sold to another company?](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#happens)**

. **[Notification of Changes.](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#change)**

. **[Contact Information.](http://blackfridaynewstoday.com/privacy-policy/#contact)**

**1\. What information does blackfridaynewstoday.com collect?**

At different times, blackfridaynewstoday.com may collect several types of information about you. Except as otherwise stated in this privacy policy, we do not provide this information to third parties, except in aggregate form.

First, we or our partners or advertisers may use a feature of your browser called a cookie to assign identification to your computer. The unique user ID contained within your cookie automatically identifies your computer – but not you – to our servers every time you visit our site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. You can turn the cookies feature off by using your browser’s preference options, but if you do so you may not be able to utilize some services properly.

Second, we keep track of your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our site. Your IP address is a number that identifies a computer which accesses the Internet. This address is used to gather broad demographic information about you, such as your Internet service provider and the geographic location of your IP address. blackfridaynewstoday.com may also collect aggregate information on how our users are utilizing the site. This might include information regarding traffic patterns through the site and search queries.

Third, we log browser types, access times, URLs from which visitors came to our site and URLs viewed by visitors while on our site. Again, blackfridaynewstoday.com uses this information on an aggregate basis, in this case making sure we can support overall visitor traffic and service performance.

Fourth, at specific times we may ask you to provide us with personal information to enable you to register for a service or to enter a sweepstakes. You may also provide personal information if you write us feedback email. This information may include but is not limited to your name and email address. You may always choose not to provide us with this information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service, offer you personalized content, or respond to your feedback.

**2\. What organization is collecting the information?**

blackfridaynewstoday.com usually collects the requested information. However, blackfridaynewstoday.com has chosen select partners to provide certain services. To use certain services on the site, it may be necessary to enter information that then goes to our partner and is not kept by blackfridaynewstoday.com. The areas of our site in which partners are collecting information may be co-branded with our partners’ logos. If you have questions regarding the privacy policy or data collection practices of one of our content partners, please contact that partner directly.

**3\. What does blackfridaynewstoday.com do with the data it collects?**

Whenever blackfridaynewstoday.com collects data, the data is intended to tailor or improve the experience of visitors to our site. From the data collected we can customize content and advertising based on the user’s preferences. We may use information from cookies to differentiate between unique users, personalize the site for each unique user, to control the frequency of individual advertisements directed to individual computers, and other purposes. In all cases, personally identifiable information is not shared with our advertisers, except as otherwise stated in this privacy policy.

We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site. It’s the way we can make sure our service is consistently available to you.

If you register for a service or to enter a sweepstakes, we may use the information we collect to provide the service to you or send communications regarding the sweepstakes. We may also send a newsletter by email to our users who opt to receive such emails. It is our policy to send these emails only to users who give us permission to do so. In every such email, we will also have instructions on how to unsubscribe to avoid receiving any future emails from us. blackfridaynewstoday.com also may contact you by email to respond to feedback you have submitted.

**4\. With whom does blackfridaynewstoday.com share data?**

blackfridaynewstoday.com may disclose your personal information to our business partners to provide you with the services you have requested, or to companies that offer a cobranded version of our site. If you have questions regarding the privacy policy or data-collection practices of one of our business partners, please contact that partner directly. blackfridaynewstoday.com does not have control over and is not responsible for the data collection and use practices of our business partners. blackfridaynewstoday.com may also disclose your personal information to other members of the blackfridaynewstoday.com family of businesses.

We also may disclose your personal information (including without limitation IP addresses) to a third party if the law or legal process requires it, to protect the rights or property of blackfridaynewstoday.com or others, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

We may disclose certain non-personally identifiable information about you to advertisers or other third parties to present you with targeted advertisements. We may share aggregate demographic information with our advertisers or information collection companies, but will not reveal any personally identifiable information in these instances.

**5\. What choices are available regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**

As previously noted, you may always choose to not provide us with any of the information we request; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service or limit our ability to offer personalized content.

**6\. How can I update or correct my information?**

blackfridaynewstoday.com does not currently have a method for users to change their user information. In the case of personalized services, you will be able to modify your user information through personalization links on those pages.

**7\. How can I delete my information?**

blackfridaynewstoday.com currently does not have a method for completely deleting user information from our database. However, deleting the cookie stored on your computer will cause you to be perceived as a new user with no known user data. You may also change a setting in your browser, instructing it not to accept cookies, but this could prevent you from receiving some blackfridaynewstoday.com services.

**8\. What procedures have been designed to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under blackfridaynewstoday.com’s control?**

Except as otherwise stated in this privacy policy, blackfridaynewstoday.com has taken measures to ensure that information that is not publicly available through its site is accessible only to the user who initially entered the information or to authorized personnel at blackfridaynewstoday.com or its partners, and only after a password has been entered. In the unlikely event of a security breach for which we provide notice under Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.82, blackfridaynewstoday.com will send a notification to the email address on file (if any) for each relevant user informing him or her of the security breach.

**9\. What about privacy policies for sites to which blackfridaynewstoday.com links?**

blackfridaynewstoday.com contains many links to Web sites not controlled by blackfridaynewstoday.com. These sites have their own policies and practices with respect to online privacy, and blackfridaynewstoday.com cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Web sites.

**10\. What happens to my information if blackfridaynewstoday.com merges with or its assets are sold to another company?**

It is possible that blackfridaynewstoday.com and/or any of our assets may be acquired. In such a transaction, user information may be transferred to the acquiring entity. While we will endeavor to require the successor company to maintain this privacy policy, we cannot guarantee that our policy will remain in effect.

**11\. Notification of Changes**

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the site. We will post our new privacy policy, along with the date of its last revision, prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check this page for information about revisions to our privacy policy.

**12\. Contact Information**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or about blackfridaynewstoday.com’s information collection practices, please submit them via the form found here: http://www.blackfridaynewstoday.com/contact-us/
